<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ashita</string>
    <string name="TermCondition">I agree to App Name <i><b><u>User Agreement</u></b></i>,
        <i><b><u>Privacy Policy</u></b></i>,  <i><b><u>Data Policy</u></b></i> and  <i><b><u>Cookies Policy</u></b></i></string>
    <string name="NeedHelp"><u><b><i>Need help? </i></b></u></string>
    <string name="tncDetails">
        <i><b><u>LICENSE AGREEMENT AND DATA POLICY FOR ASHITA APP\n\n</u></b></i>
        <i><b><u>PLEASE READ THIS SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT CAREFULLY BEFORE YOU USE ASHITA APP.
            BY CHECKING TO THE CHECKBOX YOU ARE AGREEING TO BOUND BY THE TERM OF THE LICENSE AND ALSO DATA POLICY.
            IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY OF THIS TERM OR DATA POLICY PLEASE DON’T CLICK ON THE CHECKBOX
            AND PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS ASHITA APP.\n\n</u></b></i>

        <b>1 Ashita\n</b>
        1.1 Who are we\n\n

        Ashita is a leading supplier of water filtration system for domestic, business and industries use.
        We pride ourselves in using the best filtration media from Japan, U.S.A, Korea and Taiwan filtration technology
        in all of our product. We mostly uses micro filter (Ultra filtration) pre-filter or Point-of-Entry (POE)
        Filters in ensuring a clearance and safer for human consumption. We continuously strive for products innovation
        to cater for our ever changing environment needs and our customers\' expectation and demand for safer and better
        quality to use and drink.\n\n

        1.2 Vision and goal\n\n

        Our vision and goal is to make Ashita filtration system a household name, to provide a cleaner, clearer and safer
        water for consumption. Customers\' satisfaction remains as our top priority in everything we do at Ashita.\n\n

        1.3 How do contact us\n\n

        You can directly contact us through our offical Facebook page Ashita Water or our offical Instagram Ashita_water.
        Please do not email through <i><u>noreply.ashita@gmail.com</u></i> as your email wouldn\'t be replied or been seen.\n\n

        <b>2 User of platforms\n\n</b>

        2.1 Before using any function provided by Ashita app, you will need to register an account.
        When register we will ask you to provide us with personal information such as your name, email,
        6-character password, mobile, branch and also position. Your unique password should be kept secret
        all the time. You have the responsible for not sharing your password with other. Ashita app won\'t be
        responsible for loss of password or account hacks due to you sharing your password.\n\n

        2.2 You are obliged to provide information that is correct, up to date and complete. Ashita have the right to take legal action
        if you purposely provide us with the incorrect information.\n\n

        2.3 You can request the admin to delete your account for you, but the admin have the right to modify your details or delete
        your account at any time. Ashita also have the right to keep your personal details for as long as they wants
        even when you decided to leave Ashita.\n\n

        <b>3 Restrictions\n\n</b>

        3.1 Data confidentiality\n
        The following is a non-exhaustive list of the types of data which should be keep confidential or prohibited to
        leak out of the company. Ashita reserves the right to investigate and take appropriate legal action against anyone
        who, in Ashita sole discretion, engages in leaking out any kind of data to other company, third party, friends or
        family through written documents, oral exchanges, electronic data, observation and browsing, etc. Sensitive data include,
        but are not limited to the following:\n\n

        3.1.1 any details about the filters which is being sold in the company\n\n

        3.1.2 the source the filter is being imported from\n\n

        3.1.3 the customer buy or had service from Ashita, no matter the status is terminated or active\n\n

        3.1.4 staff details which work under or work before at Ashita\n\n

        3.1.5 all the sensitive data such as email, password of any kind used in the Ashita app\n\n

        3.1.6 ways of accessing Ashita app\n\n

        3.1.7 the Apk file of Ashita app\n\n

        3.2 Activities Prohibited on the Platform\n
        The following is a non-exhaustive list of the types of conduct that are illegal or prohibited on the
        Platforms. Ashita reserves the right to investigate and take appropriate legal action against anyone who,
        in Ashita sole discretion, engages in any of the prohibited activities. Prohibited activities include, but
        are not limited to the following:\n\n

        3.2.1 using the Platforms for any purpose in violation of local, state, or federal laws or regulations\n\n

        3.2.2 posting any content that infringes the intellectual property rights, privacy rights, publicity
        rights, trade secret rights, or any other rights of any party\n\n

        3.2.3 posting content that is unlawful, obscene, defamatory, threatening, harassing,
        abusive, slanderous, hateful, or embarrassing to any other person or entity as determined by Ashita
        in its sole discretion or pursuant to local community standards\n\n

        3.2.4 posting content that constitutes cyber-bullying,as determined by Ashita in its sole discretion\n\n

        3.2.5 posting content that depicts any dangerous, life-threatening, or otherwise risky behavior\n\n

        3.2.6 posting telephone numbers, street addresses, or last names of any person\n\n

        3.2.7 posting URLs to external websites or any form of HTML or programming code\n\n

        3.2.8 posting anything that may be “spam,” as determined by Ashita in its sole discretion\n\n

        3.2.9 impersonating another person when posting content\n\n

        3.1.10 harvesting or otherwise collecting information about others, including e-mail addresses, without their consent\n\n

        3.2.11 allowing any other person or entity to use your identification for posting or viewing comments\n\n

        3.2.12 harassing, threatening, stalking, or abusing any person on the Platforms\n\n

        3.2.13 engaging in any other conduct that restricts or inhibits any other person from using or enjoying the App ,
        or which, in the sole discretion of Ashita, exposes Ashita or any of its customers, suppliers, or any other parties
        to any liability or detriment of any type\n\n

        3.2.14 encouraging other people to engage in any prohibited activities as described herein\n\n

        3.2.15 promoting other brand or service other service other than Ashita to existing or terminated customer\n\n

        3.2.16 contacting customer not for the reason of service or sales promotion\n\n

        3.2.17 tried to brute foot or any other ways to login as Admin\n\n

        3.2.18 enter any incorrect data intentionally or unintentionally\n\n

        3.3 Ashita reserves the right but is not obligated to do any or all of the following:\n\n

        3.3.1 investigate an allegation that any content posted on the Platforms does not conform to these Terms
        and determine in its sole discretion to remove or request the removal of the content\n\n

        3.3.2 remove content which is abusive, illegal, or disruptive, or that otherwise fails to conform with these Terms\n\n

        3.3.3 suspend or terminate a user’s access to the Platforms or their Ashita Account upon any breach of these Terms or any other reason\n\n

        3.3.4 monitor, edit, or disclose any content on the Platforms\n\n

        3.3.5 edit or delete any content posted on the Platforms, regardless of whether such content violates these standards\n\n

        <b>4 Customer\n\n</b>

        4.1 Adding Customer\n
        Customer will need to be added/registered before you can add register a new filter. You will need
        to ensure all the data which is being type in is correct and did not miss type or leave any of the require file blank\n\n

        4.2 Terminate/Recover Customer Details\n
        Customer can only be terminated by Admin. Customer should only be terminated/recover under the agreement of CEO and also other admins\n\n

        <b>5 Sales\n\n</b>
        5.1 Registering Filter\n
        All filter details need to be fill up according to the filter brought by the customer. Filter can only be brought after the customer had been
        added or registered. You will need to ensure all the details is correct\n\n

        5.2 Commission\n
        You need to ensure the amount of Commission you entered is being calculated correctly if not Ashita will have the right to investigate and take
        legal action if they wants to\n\n

        5.3 Serveries list\n
        This list should only be access by the staff under the sales or admin position. You will need to keep this list confidential to everyone including
        the Technician staff\n\n

        <b>6 Service\n\n</b>

        6.1 Servicing Filter\n
        You will need to ensure the filter to be at a good state and be careful along the service. You cannot add or change extra spare part just to get
        higher commissions. Your only allow to service filter which is given to you by the CEO or the sales staff\n\n

        6.2 Comission\n
        You need to ensure the amount of service price you entered is the same amount you collected from the customer if not Ashita will have the right to
        investigate and take legal action if they wants to\n\n

    </string>
</resources>
